<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Posts on ZeroDayOwl</title>
        <link>https://zerodayowl.github.io/posts/</link>
        <description>Recent content in Posts on ZeroDayOwl</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <copyright>&lt;a href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a&gt;</copyright>
        <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://zerodayowl.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
        
        <item>
            <title>Genesis</title>
            <link>https://zerodayowl.github.io/posts/2022/09/genesis/</link>
            <pubDate>Sat, 03 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            
            <guid>https://zerodayowl.github.io/posts/2022/09/genesis/</guid>
            <description>As this is the first post on my blog, I was pondering whether to start with a post like this or go straight into writing about technical stuff, but then I realized that every program, even the most obscure one, started with it’s little Hello World at first, right? So why shouldn’t this get its fair share as well?
Hiya everyone (including you and the crawlers that are currently crawling my page), you’ve probably looked through the other sections of my website already, particularly the /about section.</description>
            <content type="html"><![CDATA[


<p>As this is the first post on my blog, I was pondering whether to start with a post like this or go straight into writing about technical stuff, but then I realized that every program, even the most obscure one, started with it’s little <em>Hello World</em> at first, right? So why shouldn’t this get its fair share as well?</p>
<p>Hiya everyone (including you and the crawlers that are currently crawling my page), you’ve probably looked through the other sections of my website already, particularly the <a href="/about">/about</a> section. If you haven’t already, allow me to reintroduce myself: I’m a high school student who finds interests in computers, CTFs, development, and, yes, retired machines too! 😛</p>
<p>As I have said before, this is a blog is for keeping logs of the projects I do, my ideas and thoughts and well… my long list of side projects, which I owe an apology to for not completing, <em>yet</em>. So this might shift between being a journal, a logbook or a place where I simply rant about just anything. I’m not sure which one I’ll choose, but I’m sure I’ll have a place to put it all, in the end.</p>
<p>I believe that we learn every moment, and every learning is worth sharing, for someone around the planet. So this is my little attempt to share what I am learning, for those of you out there who are likely interested in a myriad of things like me.</p>
<p>Well I think it’s a good start, innit?</p>
]]></content>
        </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>
